Guide to the Irish Echo Photographs AIA.045
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Artists, circa 1938-2004; 6.33 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 2 card boxes, and 2 manuscript boxes
  - Subseries V.A: Individual Artists, 1925-2004
    - Cosgrave, Mary, undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Costello, Elvis, 2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Costelloe, Paul, undated (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Costner, Kevin, 1992, undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Coughlan, Mary, undated (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Coulter, Phil, 1987, 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Cox, Brian, undated (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Cox, Christina, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Cronin, Johnny, undated (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Cronkite, Walter, undated (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Crosby, Bing, undated (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Cuddy, Joe, undated (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Cunneen, Victor, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Cunningham, Johnny, undated (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Cunningham, Larry, undated (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Cunningham, Matt, undated (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Curran, Chris, undated (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Curran, Frank, undated (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Curtin, Glen, 1994, undated (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Cusack, Cyril, 1991, 1993, undated (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Daly, Joel, undated (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - D'Ambrose, Jacques (Joseph Jacques Ahearn), undated (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Dana, circa 1974, 1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 119-121, Folder 118, Folder 121)
    - Danaher, Dan, undated (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Danaher, Deirdre, 1974, 1988, undated (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Day, Dennis, undated (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Deane, Seamus, undated (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - DeBurgh, Chris, undated (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Delanty, Greg, undated (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Dempsey, Michael, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Dennehy, Brian, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Derrane, Joe, 2002-2005, undated (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Dervish, undated (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Devlin, Anne, circa 1994 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Dewhurst, Colleen, undated (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Dickins, Charles, undated (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Dillon, Matt, 1994, undated (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Doherty, Maureen, 1987, undated (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Doherty, Tom, 1987-1988, undated (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Dolan, Felix, undated (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Dolan, Joe, undated (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Donleavy, J.P., undated (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Donnelly, Donal, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 141, Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Donnelly, Terry, undated (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Doran Family, undated (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Dowling, Joe, undated (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Downey, Roma, 2000-2001, undated (Box 7, Folder 145, Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Doyle, Danny, 1995, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Doyle, Roddy, 1993-1994, 1996, undated (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Doyle, Tommy, undated (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Drew, Ronnie, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - Duffy, Patrick, undated (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Dunne, Cahal, 1996, 2003, undated (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Dunphy, Sean, undated (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Egan, John, 1990, undated (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - Egan, Seamus, 1987, undated (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Faithful, Marianne, 1992, undated (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Fallon, Ann C., circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Farrell, Paddy, 1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Farrow, Mia, 1994, undated (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Feeney, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Fitzgerald, Edward and Degeen, 1982, undated (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Fitzgerald, Geraldine, 1993, undated (Box 7, Folder 161, Box 23, Folder 30, Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Fitzgerald, Patrick, undated (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Fitzgerald, Sally, undated (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Flanagan, Fionnula, 1988, undated (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - Flanagan, Pauline, circa 1986-1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Flanagan, Thomas, undated (Box 8, Folder 2, Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Flannelly, Adrian, 1985, 1995, 2001, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Flatley, Michael, 1996, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Fleming, Madeline, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Fleming, Sean, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Flynn, Martin, 2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Foley, Connie, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Foster and Allen, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Frances, Marie, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Fricker, Brenda, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian, 1968, undated (Box 8, Folder 12, Box 23, Folder 33-34)
    - Gallagher, Bridie, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gallagher, Rory, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Gallagher, Thomas, circa 1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Galway, James, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Geldof, Bob, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - General Artists, undated (Box 20, Folder 5, Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - Gerrity, Sister Mary Beata, 1985, 1987, 1989, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Gibson, Mel, 1994, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Ginnity, Noel V., 1995, 1997, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Gleason, Jackie, 1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Gleeson, Brendan, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Glen, Iain, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Glynn, Maureen, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Grace, Brendan, 1998, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Grey, Joel, circa 1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Griffin, Marian Tomas, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Griffith, Merv, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Guthrie, Tyrone, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Hamill, Pete, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Harbison, Janet, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Harris, Jared, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Harris, Richard, 1989, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Harte, Frank, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Hayes, Gus, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Hayes, Helen, circa 1980s, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Hayes, Martin, 1995, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Hayes, P.J., undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Healy, Michael, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Healy, Shay, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Heaney, Joe, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Heaney, Seamus, 1991, 1994-1996, undated (Box 8, Folder 42, Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Heeney, Sean, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Hegarty, Dermot, 1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Henderson, Rose, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Henry, Dermot, 1986, 2003, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Henry, Noel, 1987, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Herbert, Victor, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Hill, Noel, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Hitchner, Earle, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Hope, Bob, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Hughes, Barnard, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Hunt, Helen, undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Hurley, Red, 1987, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Huston, Anjelica, circa 1993, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Hyland, Brian, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Hynes, Gerry, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Individual Artists: "A", circa 1970s, 1986-1989, 1992, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Individual Artists: "B", circa 1969, 1974, 1988-2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Individual Artists: "C", 1987-1988, 1994, 1996, 2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Individual Artists: "D", 1976, 1986-1989, 1994-1998, undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Individual Artists: "E", 1986, undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Individual Artists: "F", 1975, 1980-1981, 1990, 2002-2004, undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Individual Artists: "G", circa 1970s-1980s, 1994, 1999, undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Individual Artists: "H", 1986, 1989, 1998, 2002-2003, undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Individual Artists: "I" and "J", 1984, 1988, 1997, undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Individual Artists: "K", 1986-1993, 1997, 2003, undated (Box 8, Folder 67-68)
    - Individual Artists: "L", 1960, 1985-1986, 1994, 2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Individual Artists: "M", circa 1970, 1984-1989, 1992-2004, undated (Box 8, Folder 70-71)
    - Individual Artists: "N", circa 1970s-1980s, 1995, 1998, 2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Individual Artists: "O", 1963, circa 1975-1976, 1980-1998, 2001, 2003, undated (Box 8, Folder 73-74)
    - Individual Artists: "P", 1986-1987, 1993, 2000, undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Individual Artists: "Q", circa 1970s, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Individual Artists: "R", circa 1970s, 1985-1989, 2001-2004, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Individual Artists: "S", circa 1970s, 1987, 1992, 2002-2003, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Individual Artists: "T", 1999, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Individual Artists: "U" and "V", 1985, 2002, 2004, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Individual Artists: "W", 1986, 1995-1997, 2001, 2004, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Individual Artists: "X," "Y" and "Z", 2002, 2004, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Irish Rovers, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Ivers, Eileen, 1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Jackson, Tony, 1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Jordan, Neil, 1992, undated (Box 23, Folder 31-32, Folder 31, Box 9, Folder 8, Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Keane, Dolores, circa 1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Keane, James, 1986, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Keane, John B., 1986, 1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 11, Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Keenan, Paddy, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Kelly, Eamon, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Kelly, Gene, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Kelly, Grace, 1981, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Kennedy, William, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Kenny, Pat, 1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Kenny, Tony, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Kilbridge, Pat, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Kingston, Noel, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, Daniel Day, 1989, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Lunny, Donal, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - MacGowan, Shane, 2001, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - MacNally, John, 1987, 1994, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Madden, Joannie, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Maken, Tommy, 1998, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Mallon, Brian, 1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Maloney, Paddy, 1980, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Marcus, David, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Margo, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - McCabe, Patrick, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - McCann, Donal, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - McCarthy, Jack, circa 1950s, 1990, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - McComiskey, Billy, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - McCormack, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - McCourt, Frank, 1985-1986, 1999, undated (Box 17, Folder 31-33, Box 9, Folder 36)
    - McCourt, Malachy, 1987, 2000-2001, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - McDermot, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - McEvoy, Johnny, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - McGahern, John, circa 1994, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - McGarrigle, Kate and Anna, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - McGinty, Paddy, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - McGoldrick, Anna, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - McGonigle, Mary, 1989, 1993, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - McKenna, Siobhan, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - McKeown, Susan, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - McLaverty, Bernard, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - McNellis, Barney, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - McPhail, Jimmy, undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Moloney, Mick, 1992, 2002, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Moloney, Paddy, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Moore, Christy, 1997, undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Morrison, Van, 1994, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Mulvihill, Tommy, undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Murray, Derek (Saw Doctors), undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Murray, Ruby, undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Neeson, Liam, 1995, 1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 34, Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Nellany, Joe, undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Noonan, Paddy, 1987, 1989, circa 1993, 1995, undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - O'Brien, Dermot, undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - O'Casey, Sean, undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - O'Connell, Maura, 1982, undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - O'Connell, Robbie, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - O'Connor, Carroll, undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - O'Connor, Eamon, 1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - O'Connor, Sinead, 1992-1993, 1995, 2004, undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - O'Conor, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - O'Donnell, Daniel, 1992-1993, undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - O'Donnell, Robbie, 1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - O'Donoghue, Chris, undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - O'Dowd, Mary, undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - O'Hara, Mary, undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - O'Murchu, Liam, undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, 1987-1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - O'Neill, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - O'Shea, Milo, 1988, 1996, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - O'Shea, Richie, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - O'Sullivan, Jerry, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Owens, Michael Jesse, 1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Patterson, Frank and Eileen, 1984-1986, 1990, 1996, undated (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Quinn, Aidan, circa 1996, 2001, undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Quinn, Carmel, circa 1960s, 1988, 1995, undated (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Rea, Stephen, circa 1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 81, Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Reilly, Deirdre, undated (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Reilly, Paddy, 1988, 1995-1996, undated (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Reynolds, Paddy, undated (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Roche, Hal, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Rock, Dickie, undated (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Roper, Pat, 1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Russell, Micho, 1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Ryan, Cathie, 1998, undated (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Sands, Tommy, undated (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Shannon, Sharon, 2004, undated (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Shine, Brendan, undated (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Showalter, Julie, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Toibin, Niall, 1989, 2002, undated (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Tracey, Olivia, undated (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Treacy, Paul, undated (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Turner, Pierce, 1986, 1996, undated (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Unidentified Concert, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Individual Artists, circa 1970s, 1983-1987, 1992-1995, 2002, undated (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - White, Robert, 1978, 1993, undated (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Wynne, Martin, undated (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Yeats, William Butler, 1989, undated (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Subseries V.B: Bands, 1960-2004
    This subseries mainly contains photographs of traditional Irish showbands, as well as more contemporary Irish and Irish American bands. Some unaffiliated but extremely influential bands, such as The Beatles, are also included. Noteworthy bands featured in this subseries include The Chieftains, The Dubliners, The Irish Rovers, The Saw Doctors, and U2. The majority of these photos are bands' official publicity shots.
    - Abbey Tavern Singers, undated (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Altan, circa 1986-1987, circa 1997, 2000, 2002, undated (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Anam, undated (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Anuna, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Arcady, undated (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Artane Boys Band, undated (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Bagatelle, 1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Barley Bree, circa 1986, undated (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Battlefield Band, undated (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - The Beatles, undated (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Bergen Gaelic League Band, undated (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Big Stupid Guitars, undated (Box 9, Folder 113, Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Black 47, circa 1992-1997, undated (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Blacks Mountain, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Blackwater Boys, circa 1977, 1978, undated (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Bloo, 2000, undated (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Boomtown Rats, undated (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Boston Burglars, 1993, undated (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Boys of the Lough, 1995, undated (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Brehon Law, undated (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Bunratty Castle Singers, 1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Capercaillie, undated (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Carnloch, undated (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Celtic Cross, undated (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Celtic Fiddle Festival, 1983, undated (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Celtic Fusion, undated (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Celtic Tenors, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Celtic Thunder, undated (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Ceol Chiarrai, undated (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Cherish the Ladies, 1987, undated (Box 17, Folder 35-36, Box 9, Folder 131)
    - The Chieftains, 1975, 1977, 1988, 1990-1997, undated (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Clan Eirann Pipe Band, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Clancy Brothers, 1968, 1987-1988, 1992-1999, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Clannad, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Conquerers, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The Corrs, 1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 37, Box 23, Folder 36, Box 10, Folder 4)
    - The Cranberries, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Danu, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - De Dannon, 1983, 1985, 1996, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Mike Delahunty Showband, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Detroit Showband (Jimmy Geraghty), undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - The Devlins, circa 1993, circa 1997, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Dixies, 1960, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - The Dolan Family, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - The Drovers, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - The Druids, 1981, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Dublin City Ramblers, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Dublin City Rebels, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - The Dubliners, 1987, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Due North, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Duffy Brothers, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Eire Og (Ceile Band), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - The Emeralds, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Erin's Pride, 1986, 1993, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Feis Eireann, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Four Men and a Dog, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Four to the Bar, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - The Fureys, 1991, 1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - General Bands, 1981, 1987, 1999, 2004, undated (Box 20, Folder 6, Box 17, Folder 38, Box 10, Folder 27)
    - General Bands: "A", undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - General Bands: "B", 1966, 1988, 1994-2001, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - General Bands: "C", circa 1970s, 1981, 1987-1988, 1997-1998, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - General Bands: "D", 1987, 1989-1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - General Bands: "E", 1990, 1998, 2000, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - General Bands: "F", 1986, 994, 1997-1998, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - General Bands: "G", circa 1992-1998, 2004, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - General Bands: "H", 1989-1995, circa 2000, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - General Bands: "I", circa 1971, 1995, 2001, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - General Bands: "J", 2002 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - General Bands: "K", circa 1987, 1998, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - General Bands: "L", 1993, 2002-2003, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - General Bands: "M", 1996-1998, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - General Bands: "N", 1988, 1993-1997, 2002-2003, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - General Bands: "O", 1988-1989, circa 1998, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - General Bands: "P", circa 1976, circa 1997-2004, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - General Bands: "Q", undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - General Bands: "R", 1983-1988, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - General Bands: "S", circa 1977, 1986-1999, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - General Bands: "T", 1983-1989, circa 1999-2004, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - General Bands: "U", 2004 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - General Bands: "V", undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - General Bands: VH1 Music Festival, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - General Bands: "W", 1975, 1996-1997, undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - General Bands: "X," "Y" and "Z", circa 1994, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - The Green Fields in America, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Hair of the Dog, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Hi-Spots Showband, undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - (Sean Dunphy and the) Hoedowners, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Hudson River Bop and Phillies Diller, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Innish, undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Iona, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Irish Mist, 1989, undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Irish Ramblers, undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Irish Rovers, undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - The Irish Tenors, 1999, undated (Box 10, Folder 61, Box 17, Folder 40, Box 23, Folder 35)
    - The Irish Tenors (Ellis Island Concert), 2001 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - The Irish Tradition, undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Itinerants, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Jury's Irish Cabaret of Dublin, circa 1977, circa 1981-1987, undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Andy Kerrigan Orchestra, undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Kerry Artistes, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Kila, undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - King's Showband, undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Kips Bay Ceili Band, undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Knappogue Castle Singers, undated (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Donal Lunny Band, circa 1998, undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - McNulty Family, 1948, undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - McTrigger, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Morning Star, undated (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Patrick Street, undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - The Pogues, circa 1989, circa 1993, 1997, undated (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - The Prodigals, 1997, 1999-2002, undated (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Louis Quinn Family Showband, undated (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Royal Blue Showband, undated (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Royal Showband (Brendan Bowyer), undated (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Saw Doctors, 1992-1993, undated (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Six Priests, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Solas, 2000, undated (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Statesmen Showband, undated (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Trinity Irish Dance Company, 1997, circa 1999, undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Tulla Ceili Band, 1984, undated (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - U2, 1981, 1992-1996, undated (Box 10, Folder 86, Box 17, Folder 41-42, Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Band, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Patrick Walsh Band, undated (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Brendan Ward Orchestra, undated (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Wolfe Tones, 1975, 1990-1991, 1996, 2002, undated (Box 10, Folder 89, Box 17, Folder 43)
- Series VI: Film, Television, and Theatre, 1952, 1970-2004; 6.19 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, 1 card box, and 1 oversized flat box
  This series is comprised primarily of photographic prints from American and Irish film, television, and theatre that were advertised or otherwise featured in the Irish Echo. The majority of photos in this series are either official publicity shots distributed by production studios or snapshots taken on set. This series is further divided into two subseries.
  This series contains two subseries, both of which are organized alphabetically according to production title. Major works are listed individually. Less prominent films, television shows, and theatrical productions are featured in alphabetic sequences prefaced by "Film and Television" or "Theatre," and then followed by a letter.
  - Subseries VI.A: Film and Television, 1952, 1970-2001
    This subseries consists of photographic prints of popular Irish, American, and Irish American films and television, such as My Left Foot and In The Name of the Father, both of which were directed by Irish filmmaker Jim Sheridan. Also included are photographs from a variety of popular or successful American productions, as well as smaller independent pictures, such as The Secret of Roan Inish. The majority of photographs featured in this subseries are from the 1990s and early 2000s.
    - Addams Family, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 90)